

I'm a software engineer with a passion for well-crafted design. After 7 years of experience in web technologies, in late 2017, I changed my focus entirely to ReactJS, React Native & Javascript. I've never been happier with my choice of React.

EXPERIENCES

Freelance

(2014-2018)

- Developing Android, iOS and web applications with React Native for MyLann. All of these 3 platforms are based on a single code base. Releasing in August
- Designed and developed an official website with ReactJs and PHP for Sarpaylawka, one of the biggest book distributors & sellers in Myanmar
- Designed and developed an unofficial Yangon Bus application as a side project with React Native.
- Worked with multiple clients

Web Developer at Myanmar Links

(2011-2014)

- Worked with other developers to build internal knowledgebased system for Ooredoo Myanmar's customer champions (Call center staffs)
- Worked with other developers to build Zawgyi Mart
- Worked with other developers to build the first version of Open Myanmar Initiative
- Worked with multiple clients

SKILLS

React Native, ReactJs Javascript Laravel, PHP MySql, MongoDB

CONTACT

Email: hello@iamhein.com
Phone: +95 9965525143
Website: iamhein.com

AWARD

2nd Prize Winner

Myanmar's First Ever Hackathon powered by Ooredoo

- 76 hackers
- 17 teams
- 8 NGOs' problems
- 48 hours

INVOLVEMENT

Laravel Myanmar

2013-2014

Help translation Laravel documentation to Burmese

Open Source Soft & Open Hack Hard (Event)

Panellist

Echo Magazine

2012-2013

Write tutorials and articles for echo magazine, An online magazine for developers.

EDUCATION

B.A. in English

Dagon University (2010-2013)

ALREADY WORKED WITH THESE WELL-KNOWN COMPANIES

COCCO GIORDANO